jeffcityschools.org 2007-07-24

# 

                                               Web Privacy Statement
                                               Jefferson City Schools
            The Jefferson City Schools web site exists to inform the community about and to engage
            it in our joint mission to provide a quality education to all children. We use the site to
            publish as much information about Jefferson City Schools as possible and to enhance
            two-way communication between the district and community. Your privacy is important
            to us. Please take a moment to become familiar with our privacy statement.
                 •  Management
                    This website is hosted and managed by Jefferson City Schools in Jefferson,
                    Georgia. The site is comprised of many smaller sites representing schools and
                    offices, many with their own website administrators. All but a few of these sites
                    are hosted by Jefferson City Schools. Those schools with their own hosting
                    arrangements must also conform to this privacy policy. Principals and office
                    administrators are responsible for content published to their sites.
                 •  Statistical Reports and Cookies
                    Like publishers of most Web sites, the Jefferson City School system may collect
                    data from visitors to our site. The purpose of this data collection is to analyze
                    how people navigate the site and then use that analysis to make changes that
                    improve the user experience. This information is not used to track individual
                    users or create user profiles. The data collection process does not enable
                    Jefferson City Schools to discern who individuals are, only that a computer with a
                    specific number (IP) is accessing the web server. Typical information gathers and
                    analyzed by our statistical software includes:
                         Ø The date and time of your visit
                         Ø Pages you visited
                         Ø The web address (URL) of the link you followed to reach the site
                         Ø The domain of your internet service, e.g. www.tds.net
                         Ø The type and version of your web browser, e.g. Internet Explorer 5.0
                         Ø The operating system of your computer, e.g. Windows XP
                         Ø The site also includes third-party applications that may rely on cookies to
                             enable users to save their information and recall it later. The applications
                             that use cookies will expire the cookies when you leave the site.
                 •  Gathering of Your Personal Information
                    Some schools and offices use interactive tools on their web sites to gather
                    comments and feedback from visitors. The most popular interactive tools include
                    email feedback forms, guestbooks, and surveys. Typical information visitors are
                    invited to submit to us includes:
                         Ø Name
                         Ø Mailing Address
                         Ø Email Address
                         Ø Local School
                         Ø Affiliation, e.g. parent, teacher, etc.
PDF created with FinePrint pdfFactory trial version http://www.pdffactory.com

                   Some of these forms and surveys also include a blank space the visitor can use to
                   send us any type of comment or information. Do not use this field to convey
                   highly personal or sensitive information.
                •  Use of Your Personal Information
                   Information submitted by users to a specific school or office website is managed
                   and archived by that office. If the occasion warrants, it may be shred with other
                   appropriate staff. The Jefferson City School system does not share visitor
                   information with or sell it to third parties.
                •  Links to Other Websites
                   The Jefferson City School system website links to many web resources
                   considered educationally valuable. Each school’s webmaster also may choose to
                   link to external sites, but these sites must have an educational purpose. Principals
                   and office administrators are ultimately responsible for links published on their
                   sites.
                •  Children
                   The Jefferson City Schools website does not directly solicit or collect information
                   from children. If a child wishes to share information via a form, we recommend
                   that he/she obtain parent permission and that the parent supervise the activity. If
                   the information is published to the site via a guestbook, we urge that no
                   personally identifiable information be shared.
                •  Security
                   The Jefferson City Schools website does not solicit personal, highly confidential
                   information such as social security or credit card numbers and is not equipped to
                   guarantee highly secure transactions at this time.
                •  Contact Information
                   As the site continues to grow and improve, Jefferson City Schools may update
                   this privacy statement. We will note the change on our home pate to alert you to
                   the modifications. Please contact the superintendent if you have comments or
                   questions.
PDF created with FinePrint pdfFactory trial version http://www.pdffactory.com
